

# **Ming-Yang Ho**

- kaminyou.com
- ikaminyou@gmail.com
- github.com/Kaminyou
- linkedin.com/in/kaminyou
- +886 952792255

# Summary -

A data scientist at aetherAl with 4+ years of experience in 2D/3D computer vision, natural language processing, machine learning, and deep learning algorithms development. Besides, I am also adept at web programming, cyber security, and cryptography.

# Skills -

- Programming related
  - Python
  - •C/C++
  - PyTorch
  - ReactJS
  - MySQL
  - Docker
  - Linux
  - •Git
- Domain
  - •2D/3D computer vision
  - Natural language processing
  - Cyber security
  - Computer security

# Language -

- Mandarin (native)
- •English (TOEIC 825) [2014]
- ·Japanese (JEPT N1) [2021]

# Work experience

#### **Data Scientist**

aetherAI, Oct. 2021 - (Current)

- Developed and improved algorithms for various 2D/3D computer vision tasks.
- •Invented Kernalize Instance Normalization and published to ECCV 2022 (1st author)
- •Supported backend and security teams.

#### **Teaching Assistance (TA)**

NTU EE Machine Learning, Feb. 2021 - Jul. 2021

NTU EE Web Programming, Feb. 2021 - Jun. 2021

NTU CSIE Bioinformatics and Cheminformatics, Sep. 2020 - Jan. 2021

#### **Data Engineer Intern**

Dcard, Jun. 2020 - Dec. 2020

- Developed new recommendation algorithms and maintained ETL tasks.
- •Invented and integrated an automatic image cropping system into our production.
- •Invented an efficient model to detect cyber warriors among 1,000,000+ users.

## Software Engineer Intern

Institute of Information Science, Academa Sinica, Jul. 2019 - Aug. 2019

•Leveraged the concept of RGB channels to assist in SNP prediction.

## Education

2019~2021 Master of Science (@NTU CSIE CMDM lab) GPA 4.2 (Best thesis award) Research topics: 3D computer vision, Machine learning, Computer security

Computer Science (bioinformatics specialization)

BEBI, EECS, National Taiwan University (NTU)

Look, Listen, and Diagnose: a deep learning based comprehensive Parkinson's disease evaluation system with 3D point cloud and acoustic features

2014~2019 Doctor of Pharmacy GPA 4.1 (CS-related GPA: 4.3, Outstanding Graduate Award) \*Also got admitted to NTU CSIE in 2014.

Clinical Pharmacy

Pharmacy, College of Medicine, National Cheng Kung University (NCKU)

## Honors

### 2021 PyCon APAC Speaker

Get 3D models out of nothing: Python implementation of deep learning-based 3D models reconstruction from 2D images..

2021 PyCon TW Speaker

Implementation of a deep learning-based saliency detection system by Python

2020 HITCON Speaker

Potential Security and Privacy Issues in Novel Taiwanese National eID system

## Awards

- 2022 Best thesis award
- 2021 Multi-label Classification on CT Medical Imaging Competition, 3rd prize
- 2019 Outstanding Graduate Award

# **Recent Projects**

#### 2022 NTU wheel of dinner

Developed a dinner wheel for NTU students, which currently has 2,000+ users (https://github.com/Kaminyou/NTU-Dinner-Wheel)

2021 SUPERB: Speech processing Universal PERformance Benchmark Entrusted by NTU, CMU, MIT, and Facebook AI to build a leaderboard web server for SUPERB Benchmark. (https://superbbenchmark.org/)

## **Publications**

\*Ho, M. Y., et al. (2022) Ultra-high-resolution unpaired stain transformation via Kernelized Instance Normalization. ECCV 2022. (\*first and corresponding author)

Ho, M. Y., Kuo, M. C., et al. (2022) Look, Listen, and Diagnose: a deep learning based comprehensive Parkinson's disease evaluation system with 3D point cloud and acoustic features. [under review]

\*Ho, M. Y., \*Liu, L. C., Su, B. H., Wang, S. Y., Hsu, M. T., & Tseng, Y. J. (2021). PanGPCR: predictions for multiple targets, repurposing and side effects. *Bioinformatics*, 37(8), 1184-1186. (\*equal contribution) Ho, M. Y., et al. (2020) Potential security and privacy issues in novel Taiwanese National eID system.

TANET 2020 Ho, M. Y., Kuo, M. C., et al. (2022) A 2D camera is all you need: gait analysis with frontal-view 2D video by deep learning-based 3D estimation. [unpublished manuscript]